<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bikes on Supple Score</title>
    <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bikes on Supple Score</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:51:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="drio.github.io/supple/bikes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoky Gas Mask</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/spooky-gas-mask/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:51:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/spooky-gas-mask/</guid>
      <description>Fun, fast and responsive. I had qualms about how an aluminum race bike would do on the terrain here in Missoula, but the Gas Mask with the Compass Barlow Passes were a great combo. Fun climbing bike that accelerates well. A little on the rowdy side on the descent. No mounts for touring but a great day/event ride bike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jones Bikes Swb Complete</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/jones-bikes-swb-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:48:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/jones-bikes-swb-complete/</guid>
      <description>This bike was a surprise. Not for everyone, but is stupid fun to ride. Nimble and maneuverable for the tire size. No toe overlap even with the big tire and small size frame. Steers with more body english from the hips. Out of the box a little slow feeling with the Maxxis Chronicles. Accelerates better with Terrene Coronados set up tubeless. Comes to life with the Jones Carbon wheels and Schwalbe G-Ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialized Sequoia Expert</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/specialized-sequoia-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:39:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/specialized-sequoia-expert/</guid>
      <description>Ride and chill. Great smooth riding bike. Perfect road/gravel endurance bike. Predictable handling on descents. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t accelerate very well, but will hold speed once you get it there. Stock wheels are a little on the heavy side. Tested with ENVE/Chris King wheelset and the bike came to life. 3.5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aventon Kijote</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/aventon-kijote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:36:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/aventon-kijote/</guid>
      <description>For $600 you get a nice looking bike with a fun riding geometry. It is severely bogged down by weight. Handling is interesting. Front end steering takes some getting use to. Narrow arc of stability, then the bike just turns immediately. Rear end was actually fun, a little on the #tukt side. Also tested with some carbon 650b wheels from Irwin Cycling and the bike was transformed. Would love to see it come stock with 650b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Otso Waheela S</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/otso-waheela-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:25:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/otso-waheela-s/</guid>
      <description>Suspension corrected, adjustable rear chainstay length, super fun! If you like the Midnight Special but want a carbon fork stock, this is a price competitive option. Only bummer is the lack of mounts on the fork. Also, some issues with heel strike on the rear chainstay. I probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t ever run a suspension fork, so the Warakin would better suit me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kona Rove Nrb Dl</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/kona-rove-nrb-dl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:22:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/kona-rove-nrb-dl/</guid>
      <description>The Rove has a fun all-rounder handling that strikes a great balance between stability and responsiveness. Ideal for long rides on mixed terrain. Could potentially be your only bike as well if you don&amp;rsquo;t need race quickness. Would have been awesome if it had mounts on the fork for touring. Really reminded me of the handling of the Warbird V3 but with nice supple tires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salsa Warbird V4</title>
      <link>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/salsa-warbird-v4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:10:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>drio.github.io/supple/bikes/salsa-warbird-v4/</guid>
      <description>Warbird loses some responsiveness from V3 but has big gains in terms of utility and tire size. Great endurance gravel bike or light and fast tourer. Sizing is also different from V3, and for me seems to run shorter than expected. Think of it as a Cutthroat Lite. More responsive than the Cutthroat but takes on its utility with the three pack and low rider mounts in the front.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>